A comedy that proves love is blind.
Love and Other Disasters is a comedy, romance film directed by Alek Keshishian.
Flighty Emily "Jacks" Jackson works for the British edition of Vogue magazine.
Rather than pursue a relationship, Jacks regularly hooks up with her devoted
ex-boyfriend, James Wildstone, and lives with Peter Simon, a gay screenwriter.
When Jacks meets Argentinian photographer's assistant Paolo Sarmiento, she assumes he is gay and tries
to bring him and Peter together, unaware that Paolo is straight and in love with her.
Emily Jackson, played by Brittany Murphy.
Peter Simon, played by Matthew Rhys.
Paolo Sarmiento, played by Santiago Cabrera.
Tallulah Wentworth, played by Catherine Tate.
Finlay, played by Jamie Sives.
Felicity Wentworth, played by Stephanie Beacham.
Love and Other Disasters is a 2006 romantic comedy film
written and directed by Alek Keshishian.
It had its world premiere at the 2006 Toronto International Film Festival.
In 2008, the film had its UK premiere in London as the gala screening
for the BFI 22nd London Gay and Lesbian Film Festival.
Brittany Murphy portrays an assistant at British Vogue who is the
catalyst for a group of young friends as they try to find love.
Outfest 2007 presented the film as one of their features.
Keshishian originally wanted Gwyneth Paltrow to play
Jacks, but she was pregnant at the time.
Paltrow was later given a cameo role.
The film explores themes of new love, london,
england, vernissage, screenplay, lifestyle.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.